Hi everyone! Welcome to Nivela. In this quick video, I’m going to show you around your platform so you can navigate easily and start your learning journey.
Before we check the main page, take a look at the top-right header.
You can click this 'Aa' button to change the text size for optimal reading comfort, or click the contrast button to switch color modes.
Right next to it, you'll see your profile initial, we’ll click that in a moment!
Now, let's look at the left sidebar menu. This is your navigation hub! Here you can access the Home dashboard,
jump into exciting gamified lessons inside the Challenges tab,
look at the entire study timeline under Units, or customize accessibility controls.
At the very bottom of the sidebar, you can find support under Help, or securely exit your current session by clicking Sign out.
Back on our Home tab, your main dashboard features a personalized greeting followed by your main stats:
your Leaderboard rank, your earned Badges, and your Accuracy percentage.
Just below, the purple 'Your progress' banner displays your active points, your current login streak, and a progress bar showing how many lessons you’ve finished.
Our lessons are designed to be taken step-by-step.
As you can see, Lesson 1 is unlocked and ready to start.
However, Lesson 2 and 3 are locked with padlocks; they will open automatically as soon as you finish the first lesson!
If you want a study boost, scroll down to the Daily Challenge and click this green 'Start' button to begin a timed practice session.
Finally, let’s click on our initial at the top right. This takes us directly to the User profile page!
Here, you can update your credentials like your Name, Email, or Password using the edit icon.
You can also monitor your active unit checkpoint and see your total earned points.
And that’s it! You’re all set to master your English goals. Have fun learning with Nivela, and see you next time!